quackit.com 2010-01-02

# Privacy Policy for Quackit.com

With every domain name you register with [ZappyHost](http://www.zappyhost.com/), you get FREE hosting. 

With every new non-domain purchase thru [ZappyHost](http://www.zappyhost.com/domain_names/), you get a domain name for only $1.99. 

| 

As a visitor to Quackit.com, your privacy is important to us.

We never sell any personal information collected from this website.

## Types of Information Collected

### Log Files

As with most websites, data is collected in the web server log files. This is a commonly accepted practice and includes data such as web pages requested, date and time of request, the type of web browser used, the web page that referred the user to this website (if any), etc.

We use this information for determining things such as how popular the website is, whether traffic is increasing or decreasing over a period of time, which pages visitors find useful, the websites our traffic is coming from etc

### Cookies and Web Beacons

Cookies may be used on some pages within the website, such as logging into forums pages, or storing your preferences. Cookies and/or web beacons may also be used by third party websites who advertise on Quackit.com. These are typically used to provide more personalized advertising to visitors as well as enabling the third party to track user trends.

You can choose to disable cookies using your web browser's settings. If you do choose to disable cookies, some functions of this website (and other websites) may not work as expected.

### DoubleClick DART Cookies

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests ("interest based targeting"). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses "non personally identifiable information". It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx>

## Affiliated Websites

Some of the products and services provided on Quackit.com are made in conjunction with third party websites. You may be required to provide personal information to these third party websites in order to use their service or purchase a product. In these cases, we encourage you to read the privacy policy of the third party website.

## Enjoy this website?

  1. Add this page to your Favorites
  2. Link to this page (copy/paste into your own website or blog): 
  3. Help support Quackit by making a donation
  4. Add this page to your favorite social bookmarks sites: [](http://digg.com/submit?phase=2&url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww%2Equackit%2Ecom%2Fprivacy%5Fpolicy%2Ecfm&title=Privacy%20Policy%20for%20Quackit%2Ecom "Digg")  [](http://del.icio.us/post?url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww%2Equackit%2Ecom%2Fprivacy%5Fpolicy%2Ecfm&title=Privacy%20Policy%20for%20Quackit%2Ecom "del.icio.us")  [](http://reddit.com/submit?url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww%2Equackit%2Ecom%2Fprivacy%5Fpolicy%2Ecfm&title=Privacy%20Policy%20for%20Quackit%2Ecom "Reddit") 

Oh, and thank you for supporting Quackit!

|
